Guide to the Washington Theater Club records, 1952-1983 MS2061
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Production files, 1960-1979; MS2061 Series 1
  - Production 73--promotion - administrative, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 522)
  - Production 73--WTC extended, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 523)
  - Production 73--production staff worksheets, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 524)
  - Production 73--opening night lists, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 525)
  - Production 73--art work, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 526)
  - Production 73--cast background information, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 527)
  - Production 74, --programs Lemon Sky, Lanford Wilson., 1972 January 12-February 06 (Box 19, Folder 528)
  - Production 74--newspaper and magazine, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 529)
  - Production 74--advertisements, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 530)
  - Production 74--news releases, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 531)
  - Production 74--flyers and brochures, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 532)
  - Production 74--promotion - administrative, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 533)
  - Production 74--production staff worksheet, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 534)
  - Production 74--opening night lists, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 535)
  - Production 74--art work, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 536)
  - Production 74--cast background information, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 537)
  - Production 75 The Philanthropist - Christopher Hampton - Feb. 16-Mar. 12, 1972 Programs (Box 20, Folder 1)
    General note
    Formerly folder #538
  - Production 75 The Philanthropist - Christopher Hampton - Feb. 16-Mar. 12, 1972 Newspaper and Magazine, 1971 March 17-1972 March 15 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Formerly folder #539
  - Production 75 The Philanthropist - Christopher Hampton - Feb. 16-Mar. 12, 1972 Advertisements, 1972 February 19-March 01 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Formerly folder #540
  - Production 75 The Philanthropist - Christopher Hampton - Feb. 16-Mar. 12, 1972 News Releases, 1972 January 25-March 09 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Formerly folder #541
  - Production 75 The Philanthropist - Christopher Hampton - Feb. 16-Mar. 12, 1972 Flyers and Brochures, 1972 February 10-March 12 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Formerly folder #542
  - Production 75 The Philanthropist - Christopher Hampton - Feb. 16-Mar. 12, 1972 Promotion, 1971 March 15-28 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    Formerly folder #543
  - Production 75 The Philanthropist - Christopher Hampton - Feb. 16-Mar. 12, 1972 Production Staff Worksheets, 1972 February 16-March 12 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    Formerly folder #544
  - Production 75 The Philanthropist - Christopher Hampton - Feb. 16-Mar. 12, 1972 Opening Night Lists, 1972 February 16 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    Formerly folder #545
  - Production 75 The Philanthropist - Christopher Hampton - Feb. 16-Mar. 12, 1972 Art Work, 1972 February 16-March 12 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    Formerly folder #546
  - Production 75 The Philanthropist - Christopher Hampton - Feb 16-Mar. 12, 1972 Cast Background, 1972 February 16-March 12 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    Formerly folder #547
  - Production 76 Washington Square - Kenneth Jerome & Jerome Walman - Mar. 22-Apr. 16, 1972 Programs, 1972 March 22-April 16 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    Formerly folder #548
  - Production 76 Washington Square - Kenneth Jerome & Jerome Walman - Mar. 22-Apr. 16, 1972 Newspaper and Magazine, 1972 March 01-April 14 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    Formerly Folder #549
  - Production 76 Washington Square - Kenneth Jerome & Jerome Walman - Mar. 22-Apr. 16, 1972 Advertisements, 1972 March 22-April 16 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    Formerly folder # 550
  - Production 76 Washington Square - Kenneth Jerome & Jerome Walman - Mar. 22-Apr. 16, 1972 News Releases, 1972 February 25-April 12 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    Formerly folder #551
  - Production 76 Washington Square - Kenneth Jerome & Jerome Walman - Mar. 22-Apr. 16, 1972 Promotion, 1971 August 01-1972 June 26 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    Formely folder #552
  - Production 76 Washington Square - Kenneth Jerome & Jerome Walman - Mar. 22-Apr. 16, 1972 Production Staff Worksheets, 1972 March 20 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    Formerly folder #553
  - Production 76 - Washington Square - Kenneth Jerome & Jerome Walman - Mar. 22-Apr. 16, 1972 Opening Night Lists, 1972 March 06-22 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    Formerly folder #554
  - Production 76 Washington Square - Kenneth Jerome & Jerome Walman - Mar. 22-Apr. 16, 1972 Art Work, 1972 March 22-April 16 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    Formerly folder #555
  - Production 77 Four Minus One - The Basement - H. Pinter- Deadly Delilah - R. Bond - & Animal - O. Hailey Apr.26-May 21, 1972 Programs, 1972 April 26-May 21 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Formerly Folder #556
  - Production 77 Four Minus One- The Basement- H. Pinter- Deadly Delilah - R. Bond - & Animal - O. Hailey Apr.26-May 21, 1972 Newspapers and Magazine, 1972 April 14-May 06 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    Formerly Folder #557
  - Production 77 Four Minus One - The Basement - H. Pinter- Deadly Delilah - R. Bond - & Animal - O. Hailey Apr.26-May 21, 1972 Advertisements, 1972 April 25-May 09 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    Formerly Folder #558
  - Production 77 Four Minus One - The Basement - H. Pinter- Deadly Delilah - R. Bond - & Animal - O. Hailey Apr.26-May 21, 1972 New Releases, 1972 April 05-May 03 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    Formerly Folder #559
  - Production 77 Four Minus One - The Basement - H. Pinter- Deadly Delilah - R. Bond - & Animal - O. Hailey Apr.26-May 21, 1972 Promotion, 1972 April 20-May 22 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    Formerly Folder #560
  - Production 77 Four Minus One - The Basement - H. Pinter- Deadly Delilah - R. Bond - & Animal - O. Hailey Production Staff Worksheets, 1972 April 26-May 21 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    Formely Folder #561
  - Production 77 Four Minus One - The Basement - H. Pinter- Deadly Delilah - R. Bond - & Animal - O. Hailey Apr.26-May 21, 1972 Opening Night Lists, 1972 May 21-April 26 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    Formerly Folder #562
  - Production 77 Four Minus One - The Basement - H. Pinter- Deadly Delilah - R. Bond - & Animal - O. Hailey Art Work, 1972 April 26-May 21 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    Forlerly Folder #563
  - Production 78 Lady Audley's Secret - adapted by D. Seale-May 31-July 16, 1972 Programs production 78 Lady Audley's Secret- Adapted by D.Seale - May 31-July 16,1972 Programs, 1972 May 31-July 16 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    Formerly Folder #564
  - Production 78 Lady Audley's Secret- adapted by D. Seale - May 31-July 16, 1972 Newspaper and Magazine, 1972 May 18-July 13 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    Formerly Folder #565
  - Production 78 Lady Audley's Secret- adapted by D. Seale - May 31-July 16, 1972 Advertisements, 1972 May 31-July 16 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    Formerly Folder #566
  - Production 78 Lady Audley's Secret- adapted by D. Seale - May 31-July 16, 1972 News Releases, 1972 April 17-June 17 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    Formerly Folder #567
  - Production 78 Lady Audley's Secret- adapted by D. Seale - May 31-July 16, 1972 Flyers and Brochures, Circa 1972 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    Formerly Folder #568
  - Production 78 Lady Audley's Secret- adapted by D. Seale - May 31-July 16, 1972 Promotion, 1966 May 12-1972 October 16 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    Formerly Folder #569
  - Production 78 Lady Audley's Secret- adapted by D. Seale - May 31-July 16, 1972 WTC Extended, 1972 June 12-29 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    Formerly Folder #570
  - Production 78 Lady Audley's Secret- adapted by D. Seale - May 31-July 16, 1972 Production Staff Worksheets, Circa 1972 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    Formerly Folder#571
  - Production 78 Lady Audley's Secret- adapted by D. Seale - May 31-July 16, 1972 Opening Night Lists, 1972 May 31 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    Formerly Folder #572
  - Production 78 Lady Audley's Secret- adapted by D. Seale - May 31-July 16, 1972 Art Work, 1972 May 31-July 16 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    Formerly Folder #573
  - Scripts, Gallagher, Michael- The Threshing Floor, undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
    Formerly Folder #574
  - Production 79--programs Spread Eagle Papers, A Topical Revue., 1972 September 27-October 29 (Box 22, Folder 575)
  - Production 79--newspaper and magazine, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 576)
  - Production 79--advertisements, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 577)
  - Production 79--news releases, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 578)
  - Production 79--promotion - administrative, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 579)
  - Production 79--production staff worksheets, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 580)
  - Production 79--opening night lists, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 581)
  - Production 79--art work, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 582)
  - Production 80, The Rapists, Dennis Turner. --programs, 1972 November 08-December 03 (Box 22, Folder 583)
  - Production 80--newspaper and magazine, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 584)
  - Production 80--advertisements, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 585)
  - Production 80--news releases, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 586)
  - Production 80--promotion - administrative, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 587)
  - Production 80--production staff worksheets, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 588)
  - Production 80--art work, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 589)
  - Production 80--cast background information, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 590)
  - Production 81 The Boys from Syracuse - George Abbott - Programs, 1972 December 13-1973 January 07 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Formerly Folder #591
  - Production 81 The Boys from Syracuse - George Abbott - Dec.13, 1972-Jan.7,1973 Newspaper and Magazine, 1972 December 12-21 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Formerly Folder #592
  - Production 81 The Boys from Syracuse - George Abbott - Dec.13, 1972-Jan.7,1973 Advertisements, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Formerly folder #593
  - Production 81 The Boys from Syracuse - George Abbott - Dec.13, 1972-Jan.7,1973 New Releases, 1972 December 26 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Formerly Folder #594
  - Production 81 The Boys from Syracuse - George Abbott - Dec.13, 1972-Jan.7,1973 Promotion, 1972 September 29-1973 February 23 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Formerly Folder #595
  - Production 81 The Boys from Syracuse - George Abbott - Dec.13, 1972-Jan.7,1973 Production Staff worksheets, 1972 December 13-1973 January 07 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    Formerly Folder #596
  - Production 81 The Boys from Syracuse - George Abbott - Dec.13, 1972-Jan.7,1973 Art Work, 1972 December 13-1973 January 07 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    Formerly Folder #597
  - Production 82 Ceremonies in Dark Old Men - Lonne Elder, III - Jan.17-Feb.11 & Mar.6- Apr.8 1973 Programs, 1973 January 17-April 08 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    Formerly Folder#598
  - Production 82 Ceremonies in Dark Old Men - Lonne Elder, III - Jan.17-Feb.11 & Mar.6- Apr.8 1973 Newspaper & Magazine, 1973 January 13-March 18 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    Formerly Folder #599
  - Production 82 Ceremonies in Dark Old Men - Lonne Elder, III - Jan.17-Feb.11 & Mar.6- Apr.8 1973 Advertisements, 1973 January 17-May 08 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    Formerly Folder #600
  - Production 82 Ceremonies in Dark Old Men - Lonne Elder, III - Jan.17-Feb.11 & Mar.6- Apr.8 1973 New Releases, 1973 January 17-March 22 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    Formerly Folder #601
  - Production 82 Ceremonies in Dark Old Men - Lonne Elder, III - Jan.17-Feb.11 & Mar.6- Apr.8 1973 Flyers & Brochures, Circa 1973 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    Formely Folder #602
  - Production 82 Ceremonies in Dark Old Men - Lonne Elder, III - Jan.17-Feb.11 & Mar.6- Apr.8 1973 Promotion, 1969 February 15-1973 December 30 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    Formerly Folder #603
  - Production 82 Ceremonies in Dark Old Men - Lonne Elder, III - Jan.17-Feb.11 & Mar.6- Apr.8 1973 Production Staff Worksheets, 1973 January 13-February 11 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    Formerly Folder #604
  - Production 82 Ceremonies in Dark Old Men - Lonne Elder, III - Jan.17-Feb.11 & Mar.6- Apr.8 1973 Opening Night Lists (Box 23, Folder 15)
    Formerly Folder #605
  - Production 82 Ceremonies in Dark Old Men - Lonne Elder, III - Jan.17-Feb.11 & Mar.6- Apr.8 1973 Art Work (Box 23, Folder 16)
    Formerly Folder #606
  - Production 82 Ceremonies in Dark Old Men - Lonne Elder, III - Jan.17-Feb.11 & Mar.6- Apr.8 1973 Cast Background (Box 23, Folder 17)
    Formerly Folder #607
  - Production 83, The Enclave, Arthur Laurents. --programs, 1973 February 21-March 18 (Box 24, Folder 608)
  - Production 83--newspaper and magazine, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 609)
  - Production 83--advertisements, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 610)
  - Production 83--news releases, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 611)
  - Production 83--flyers and brochures, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 612)
  - Production 83--promotion - administrative, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 613)
  - Production 83--production staff worksheets, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 614)
  - Production 83--opening night lists, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 615)
  - Production 83--art work, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 616)
  - Production 83--cast background information, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 617)
  - Production 84, --programs Scenes from American Life, A. R. Gurney., 1973 March 28-April 22 (Box 24, Folder 618)
  - Production 84--newspaper and magazine, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 619)
  - Production 84--advertisements, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 620)
  - Production 84--news releases, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 621)
  - Production 84--flyers and brochures, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 622)
  - Production 84--promotion - administrative, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 623)
  - Production 84--production staff worksheets, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 624)
  - Production 84--art work, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 625)
  - Production 84--cast beckground information, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 626)
  - Production 85, --programs The Ecstasy of Rita Joe, George Ryga, 1973 May 02-27 (Box 24, Folder 627)
  - Production 85--newspaper and magazine, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 628)
  - Production 85--advertisements, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 629)
  - Production 85--news releases, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 630)
  - Production 85--flyers and brochures, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 631)
  - Production 85--promotion - administrative, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 632)
  - Production 85--production staff worksheets, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 633)
  - Production 85--opening night lists, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 634)
  - Production 85--art work, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 635)
  - Production 85--cast background information, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 636)
  - Production 86, Something Wild, Tennessee Williams. --programs, 1973 June 06-July 01 (Box 25, Folder 637)
  - Production 86--newspaper and magazine, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 638)
  - Production 86--advertisements, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 639)
  - Production 86--news releases, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 640)
  - Production 86--flyers and brochures, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 641)
  - Production 86--promotion - administrative, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 642)
  - Production 86--production staff worksheets, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 643)
  - Production 86--art work, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 644)
  - Production 87, Inner City, Eve Merrian and Helen Miller, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 645)
  - Production 88, Difficult Borning, Sylvia Plath, 1973 November 15-25 (Box 25, Folder 646)
  - Production 89, Thoughts, Lamar Alford, 1974 January 23-February 17 (Box 25, Folder 647)
  - Production 90, Behind the Broken Words, Roscoe Lee Browne and Anthony Zerbe, 1974 March 08-24 (Box 25, Folder 648)
  - Non-Equity Production 1, The Winter Peach, Herb Rodgers, 1963 August 06-24 (Box 26, Folder 649)
  - Non-Equity Production 2, Miss Amurica, 1963 November 12-December 08 (Box 26, Folder 650)
  - Non-Equity Production 3, Ondine, Jean Giradoux, 1964 August 03-05 (Box 26, Folder 651)
  - Non-Equity Production 4, Zoo Story and The Sandbox, Edward Albee Summer, Waiting for Godot, Samuel Beckett. Aug. 2, 7-9, 14-16,1964. The Dumbwaiter and The Collection, Harold Pinter. Aug. 21-23,28-30, 1964 September 04-06 (Box 26, Folder 652)
  - Non-Equity Production 5, The Death of Bessie Smith, Edward Albee. Play, Samuel Beckett, 1965 August 05-22 (Box 26, Folder 653)
  - Non-Equity Production 6, The Black Experience, Damon Kenyatte, 1970 August 19-26 (Box 26, Folder 654)
  - Non-Equity Production 7, Senior Prom, Jack Hofsiss and Bill Bremer, by Georgetown University, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 655)
  - Non-Equity Production 8, Warp, 1973 September 11-October 07 (Box 26, Folder 656)
  - Non-Equity Production 9, Jacques Brel Is Alive and Well and Living in Paris, Cohen Assoc., 1974 May 24-June 23 (Box 26, Folder 657)
  - Non-Equity Production 10, Jersey Plates - a rock and roll show, 1974 July 16 (Box 26, Folder 658)
  - Scripts, Alexander, Ronald - Time Out for Ginger, undated (Box 27, Folder 659)
  - Scripts, Alford, Lamar - Thoughts (Production 89), undated (Box 27, Folder 660)
  - Scripts, Austin, Paul John - Untitled Play, undated (Box 27, Folder 661)
  - Scripts, Bakst, Janet - Jake and Naomi (Staged Reading Series), undated (Box 27, Folder 662)
  - Scripts, Balestrino, Philip - Willyum (Staged Reading 6), undated (Box 27, Folder 663)
  - Scripts, Bernard Shaw! an Incorrigible, Histrionic Montebank, undated (Box 27, Folder 664)
  - Scripts, Bevan, Donald & Edmund Trzcinski - Stalag 17, undated (Box 27, Folder 665)
  - Scripts, Bond, Raleigh - The Deadly Delilah (Production 77), undated (Box 27, Folder 666)
  - Scripts, Brown, Sterling - Senator Billboard Rawkins, undated (Box 27, Folder 667)
  - Scripts, Caddic, Regis - Closets, an Experience in Two Acts, undated (Box 27, Folder 668)
  - Scripts, Cartwright, Glen - Mother's Day, undated (Box 27, Folder 669)
  - Scripts, Casey, Gene & Gordon Richmond - The Magic Weave, undated (Box 27, Folder 670)
  - Scripts, Chernozemsky, Vladimir - Now Is the Time, and Other Poetry, undated (Box 27, Folder 671)
  - Scripts, Clifford, John - Wild Bill (Staged Reading 33), undated (Box 27, Folder 672)
  - Scripts, Cohen, Robert - The Death of Morris Biedermann (Staged Reading 1), undated (Box 28, Folder 673)
  - Scripts, Crinkley, Richmond - Dionysus Wants You - An Adaptation of Euripides' The Bacchae, undated (Box 28, Folder 674)
  - Scripts, Crivella, James - Now!, undated (Box 28, Folder 675)
  - Scripts, Crivella, James - Pop Corn (Staged Reading 16), undated (Box 28, Folder 676)
  - Scripts, Croswell, Anne & Lee Pockriss - Ernest in Love (Production 25), undated (Box 28, Folder 677)
  - Scripts, Croswell, Anne & Lee Pockriss - Ernest in Love (Production 25), undated (Box 28, Folder 678)
  - Scripts, Dabbs, Lowell - Amelia, undated (Box 28, Folder 679)
  - Scripts, De Grazia, Edward - The Saga of Hoo Fasa (Staged Reading 2), undated (Box 28, Folder 680)
  - Scripts, Diaz, Jorge - Requiem for a Sunflower (Special Production 6), undated (Box 28, Folder 681)
  - Scripts, Dickson, Wallace G. - The Shuttin' o' the Door, undated (Box 28, Folder 682)
  - Scripts, Donohue, M. Neal -Celebration, undated (Box 29, Folder 683)
  - Scripts, Dow, David - Master Banzo, undated (Box 29, Folder 684)
  - Scripts, Dunster, Mark - Weekend, undated (Box 29, Folder 685)
  - Scripts, Eaton, Dan - Eddie, undated (Box 29, Folder 686)
  - Scripts, Edwards, Garner - The Housewife, undated (Box 29, Folder 687)
  - Scripts, Edwards, Garner - The Night Jimmy Hand Died, undated (Box 29, Folder 688)
  - Scripts, Epstein, David - Popcorn, Bring It with You When You Come, undated (Box 29, Folder 689)
  - Scripts, Eytinge, Louis Victor - The Man under Cover, undated (Box 29, Folder 690)
  - Scripts, Feld, Bruce - Duel, undated (Box 29, Folder 691)
  - Scripts, Filson, Brent - On a Cambodian Highway, undated (Box 29, Folder 692)
  - Scripts, Fire, Richard Jersey Plates (Non-Equity Production 10), undated (Box 29, Folder 693)
  - Scripts, Richard - Forbes, Jan - Aloysius Stubbs, or the Perfect Janitor, undated (Box 29, Folder 694)
  - Scripts, Forbes, Jan - Bye, Bye, High Life, undated (Box 29, Folder 695)
  - Scripts, Forbes, Jan - Overtime, undated (Box 30, Folder 696)
  - Scripts, Forbes, Jan - The Portrait, undated (Box 30, Folder 697)
  - Scripts, Forbes, Jan - The Two Wise Men, undated (Box 30, Folder 698)
  - Scripts, Fotini Vourlekis, undated (Box 30, Folder 699)
  - Scripts, Gallagher, Michael - Dialog, undated (Box 30, Folder 700)
  - Scripts, Gallagher, Michael - Dragons Live Forever, undated (Box 30, Folder 701)
  - Scripts, Gallagher, Michael - The Leopards of Boetia, undated (Box 30, Folder 702)
  - Scripts, Gallagher, Michael- The Return of the Hero, undated (Box 30, Folder 703)
  - Scripts, Gallagher, Michael- Return to Dutton, undated (Box 30, Folder 704)
  - Scripts, Gallagher, Michael- These Stubborn Ones, undated (Box 30, Folder 705)
  - Scripts, Gallagher, Michael- The Threshing Floor, undated (Box 30, Folder 706)
  - Scripts, Gallagher, Michael- The Week the Stars Fell, undated (Box 30, Folder 707)
  - Scripts, Garcia, John David - Baruch (the Trial of S inoza), undated (Box 30, Folder 708)
  - Scripts, Gardner, Herb - A Thousand Clowns, undated (Box 31, Folder 709)
  - Scripts, Gilhooley, Jack - Avenue B, undated (Box 31, Folder 710)
  - Scripts, Gilhooley, Jack - The Comeback, undated (Box 31, Folder 711)
  - Scripts, Goldberg, Robert - Just for Fun My Dears, undated (Box 31, Folder 712)
  - Scripts, Gonzalez, Gloria - Revue Sketches, undated (Box 31, Folder 713)
  - Scripts, Gordon, Robert - The Light and the Dark of It, undated (Box 31, Folder 714)
  - Scripts, Gregory, Augusta, Lady - The Rising of the Moon (Production 10), undated (Box 31, Folder 715)
  - Scripts, Gressieker, Hermann - Royal Gambit, Translated & Adapted by George White, undated (Box 31, Folder 716)
  - Scripts, Haag, John - The Portrait, undated (Box 31, Folder 717)
  - Scripts, Hailey, Oliver - Animal (Production 77), undated (Box 31, Folder 718)
  - Scripts, Hailey, Oliver - Continental Divide (Production 60), undated (Box 31, Folder 719)
  - Scripts, Hailey, Oliver - Father's Day (Production 69), undated (Box 31, Folder 720)
  - Scripts, Hailey, Oliver - Who's Happy Now? (Production 51), undated (Box 31, Folder 721)
  - Scripts, Halpert, Joanna Marie - The Ice Wolf, a Tale of the Eskimos, a Play for Young People, undated (Box 31, Folder 722)
  - Scripts, Harnick, Sheldon & Jerry Bock - The Apple Tree- a New Musical (Additional Book Material by Jerome Coopersmith), undated (Box 32, Folder 723)
  - Scripts, Heldt, Jane - Relating to the Lexington Affair, undated (Box 32, Folder 724)
  - Scripts, Herbert, Hugh - The Moon Is Blue, undated (Box 32, Folder 725)
  - Scripts, Heyward, Dubose & Dorothy - Porgy, undated (Box 32, Folder 726)
  - Scripts, Himelfarb, Marvin F. - Hank Is My Name, undated (Box 32, Folder 727)
  - Scripts, Himelfarb, Marvin F. - Our Next Lucky Contestant Is..., undated (Box 32, Folder 728)
  - Scripts Himelfarb, Marvin F. - You Can't Sell Cornbeef in July, undated (Box 32, Folder 729)
  - Scripts, Hirshfield, Robert - The Cage, undated (Box 32, Folder 730)
  - Scripts, Hirshfield, Robert - The Reality Caper, undated (Box 32, Folder 731)
  - Scripts, Hoggard, James Conspiracy, undated (Box 32, Folder 732)
  - Scripts, Hoggard, James - Morganatic Marriage, undated (Box 32, Folder 733)
  - Scripts, Hoggard, James - Swinger, undated (Box 32, Folder 734)
  - Scripts, Horowitz, Terry Fred - High and Low Relief, undated (Box 32, Folder 735)
  - Scripts, Hosford, Robert - The Smiling Dragon, undated (Box 32, Folder 736)
  - Scripts, Howard, Sidney - Madam, Will You Walk?, undated (Box 32, Folder 737)
  - Scripts, Hudley, William - Yesterday I Had the Blues, undated (Box 33, Folder 738)
  - Scripts, Hungarian Love Call, undated (Box 33, Folder 739)
  - Scripts, Ionesco, Eugene - Rhinoceros, undated (Box 33, Folder 740)
  - Scripts, Jacobs, Fred Rue - Snow Job, undated (Box 33, Folder 741)
  - Scripts, Johnson, Wallace - Into the Sun, undated (Box 33, Folder 742)
  - Scripts, Jones, Vonnye & Harold Adams - The Fourth State, or Love by the Numbers, or even Lysistrata Reversed. Lyrics by Vonnye Jones, Arrangements by Forrest Brubaker, undated (Box 33, Folder 743)
  - Scripts, Kaufman, George S. - If Men Played Cards As Women Do, undated (Box 33, Folder 744)
  - Scripts, Kaufman, George S. - The Still Alarm, undated (Box 33, Folder 745)
  - Scripts, Kennedy, Lucy - The Pied Piper of Hamelin, A Play for Children, undated (Box 33, Folder 746)
  - Scripts, Kistner, Arthur - The Choices, undated (Box 33, Folder 747)